<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Luca Allodi @ TU/e</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Luca Allodi @ TU/e</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 16:29:18 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 13:13:53 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Office: MF 6.122a P.O. Box 513, 5600 MB Eindhoven, The Netherlands Email: l.allodi at tue.nl PGP fngrprnt: 950E 3DC8 EB66 DFF3 B64D 7848 A0AD 0BB6 5DC4 98F1  Public key here.
Curriculum Vitae
I DO NOT have a Facebook profile. My LinkedIn page (hardly updated) is this. My Twitter handle is @securescientist.
More verbosely I am an Assistant Professor at the Security Group of the Eindhoven University of Technology, in the Netherlands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 16:29:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Courses Offensive Computer Security (2IC80) This is an introductory course on hacking, with a focus on computer networks and software. The full course will revolve around the idea that (most) mechanisms can be illegitimately misused to obtain (some level of) a desired behaviour; this is the very essence of computer security. We will explore network protocols and the implied trust relations they operate upon; we will look at software vulnerabilities and at how they can emerge from software code; we will look at exploit testing and automated attack frameworks; we will look at penetration testing and advanced networked attacks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 16:09:06 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Funded projects TBA
MSc Projects Available Schedule an appointment with me.
Current    Student Where Topic     Jose Luis Torre Arce TU/e Quality control in the underground   Jeroen Ubbink  TU/e weapons trafficking   René Wouters TU/e drug vendors/buyers profiling   Tzouliano Chotza KPMG Phishing response   Ivan Kozlov DELOITTE Malware engineering techniques   Rik Dolfing RU SOC sign.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 13:07:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/</guid>
      <description>I am one of the authoring member of the First.org/NIST Common Vulnerability Scoring System Standard. First.org CVSS Special Interest Group (Authoring member). Common Vulnerability Scoring System (CVSS) v3. Published at http://www.first.org/cvss.
Highlights Amber van der Heijden, Luca Allodi. Cognitive Triaging of Phishing Attacks. In Proceedings of Usenix Security 2019 (to appear).
 Luca Allodi. 2017. Economic Factors of Vulnerability Trade and Exploitation. In Proceedings of the 2017 ACM SIGSAC Conference on Computer and Communications Security (CCS &amp;lsquo;17).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>